Bennet, Augustus W.; Papers apap225
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Scrapbook Eight, 1944 October (Oversized 3)
- Scrapbook Nine, 1944 October-November (Oversized 6)
- Scrapbook Ten, 1944 October-1945 April (Oversized 7)
- Scrapbook Eleven, 1944 November-1945 January (Oversized 3)
- Scrapbook Twelve, 1945 March-June (Oversized 7)
- Scrapbook Thirteen, 1945 April-1946 April (Oversized 1)
- Scrapbook Fourteen, 1946 April-June (Oversized 6)
- Scrapbook Fifteen, 1946 June-August (Oversized 8)
- Scrapbook Sixteen, 1948 January-October (Oversized 4)
- Selective Service (1 of 2), 1945-1946; Undated (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Selective Service (1 of 2), 1945-1946; Undated (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Shannon- Bennet (1 of 2), 1944-1946 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Shannon- Bennet (2 of 2), 1944-1946 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Shannon- Personal (1 of 2), 1944-1946; Undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Shannon- Personal (2 of 2), 1944-1946; Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Small Businesses- Seal, 1944-1945; Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Smith, Caroline, 1945-1946 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Smith, Mr. Harland N., 1944 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Social Security, 1944-1946; Undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Song Sheets, 1935; 1939; 1944 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Spain, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Special Enrollment Forms, Undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Speech WGNY, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Speeches, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Speeches (1 of 4), 1945; Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Speeches (2 of 4), 1945; Undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Speeches (3 of 4), 1945; Undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Speeches (4 of 4), 1945; Undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Speeches (1 of 2), 1946; Undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Speeches (2 of 2), 1946; Undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Speeches- Lincoln Day, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Sprague, Mr. Floyd L., 1944 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- St. George, Mrs., 1944 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Stanley, Mr. James, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Starr, Wilton P., 1944 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Stationary Room, Seal, 1945-1946 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Stratton, Earl (Letter), 1944 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Subscription, Charities, Contributions, etc., 1944 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Sugar, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Suggested Speech by Blackburn Hughes, Undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Sullivan County Lists, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Sullivan County Show Removal, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Sully, Myra, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Surplus Property, 1945-1946; Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Surplus Property (1 of 3), 1946 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Surplus Property (2 of 3), 1946 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Surplus Property (3 of 3), 1946 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Surplus Reporter, 1945-1946 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- T- General, 1945; Undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Total Enrollment and Registration (First Assembly, District Orange County), 1943-1944 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Towler, Col. Gray B. Tower, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Trainer, Mr. Thomas, Undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Tribute to the Flag, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- U- General, 1945; Undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
- U.N.R.R.A (United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Authority), 1943-1944; 1946 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- U.S. Empl. Comm., 1946 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- V- General, Undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Van Cleek- Madden Printing Co., 1944 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Van Hyper, George S., 1944 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Vandercook, Mr. John W., 1944; Undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
- W- General (1 of 2), 1945; Undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
- W- General (2 of 2), 1945; Undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Wall Radio Addresses (Middletown), Undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
- War Food Admin, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Waterman, Mr. Edmund, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Welsh, J.K., 1946 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- WGNY Radio Addresses (1 of 2), 1944; Undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
- WGNY Radio Addresses (2 of 2), 1944; Undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
- White, Mr. Walter, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Wightman, Mrs. Gordon, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Williams, Paul, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Wilson, Mrs. Jean Rushmore Patterson, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Wilson, Mrs. John H., 1944 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Wirths, Roland P., 1944 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- W.L.B (War Labor Board), 1945-1946 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Wolf, Mr. P.A., 1944 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Wood, Mr. Glen (Master of Mountain Ville Grange), 1944 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Workers' Questions and Answers, Undated (Box 14, Folder 38)
- W.P.B, 1945; Undated (Box 14, Folder 39)
- W.P.B, 1945-1946; Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
- W.P.B, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Wyer, Mr. A.C., 1944 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Wyer, Mr. Robert, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 4)